# KITIPAT PANCHANG

# WEP APPICATION

**O** 099-165-3222

kittipat.bear1402@gmail.com

https://kitipat.netlify.app/

1/1176 Village No. 14, Bang Wua Subdistrict, Bang Pakong District, Chachoengsao Province

## **ABOUT ME**

I am passionate about working with expert teams to learn and gain experience in system analysis and development. My goal is to create innovations and technologies that improve efficiency while adapting to constantly changing technology trends to support organizational growth and success.

#### **SKILLS**

## Web Development:

- PHP
- Laravel
- HTM
- CSS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Angular
- Msql

## Photography

 DSLR cameras, lighting setups, and image editing with Adobe Lightroom

# **EDUCATION**

## **Chiang Mai University**

May 2022 – Present I GPA: 2.68

# Nawaminthrachinuthit Triam Udomsuksa Pattanakarn School

May 2015 – April 2022 | GPA: 2.98

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Awarded "Winner of the New Gen Energy Research Showcase (Year 2)"

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **WEB DEVELOPMENT**

Present (2022-2024)

Web Programming | Chiang Mai University

- Basic website html about e-commerce, rent, booking use for CRUD
- Developed a food menu recommendation website using the Laravel Framework.
- Developed website using angular pull api to chart, news and exchange current for web stock
- Designed a CRUD system with Role-Based Access Control (RBAC).
- · Handled both Frontend and Backend development.

## **CREATIVE SOLUTION**

(2023-2024)

New Gen Energy Research Showcase | Bangkok

- Developed a project related to tourism via electric trains using a mobile application.
- Conducted user interviews and designed features to address user needs using Figma.

# Photography & Video Editor | Chiang Mai University

- Worked on the media team, capturing photos and designing posters for university events.
- Created and edited videos for Hackathon presentations and student guidance.

## **MANAGEMENT IT**

(2024)

Chiang Mai University

- Managed the "Photo Booth" at the Open House event& Outdoor cinema.
- Provided photography services, printed 4x6 inch photos, and uploaded digital copies to Google Drive & Laravel.